A Guide to the Arthur M. Squires Papers, 1888-1987 (Bulk 1940-1986)
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- D Series, Diaries, 1951-1982.
  - Box D-2, 1951-1963. (Box 70)
    - Daily Diary, 12/5/62-1/20/63.
  - Box D-3, 1963-1968. (Box 71)
    - Daily Diary, 1/20/63-2/21/63.
    - Daily Diary, 2/22/63-4/20/63.
    - Daily Diary, 4/20/63-7/3/63.
    - Daily Diary, 7/3/63-8/7/63.
    - Daily Diary, 8/7/63-9/7/63.
    - Daily Diary, 8/8/63-12/4/63.
    - Daily Diary, 12/4/63-5/5/64.
    - Daily Diary, 5/5/64-9/17/64.
    - Daily Diary, 8/18/64-12/24/64.
    - Daily Diary, 12/24/64-5/14/65.
    - Daily Diary, 9/4/65-2/8/66.
    - Daily Diary, 2/8/66-4/8/66.
    - Daily Diary, 4/8/66-7/13/66.
    - Daily Diary, 7/13/66-11/28/66.
    - Daily Diary, 11/28/66-6/27/66.
    - Daily Diary, 6/22/68-11/2/68.
  - Box D-4, 1960-1980. (Box 72)
    - Daily Diary, 11/2/68-9/10/71.
    - Daily Diary, 8/31/70-10/20/77.
    - Daily Diary, 9/11/71-12/20/75.
    - Daily Diary, 12/20/75-8/14/76.
    - Daily Diary, 10/20/77-1/31/79.
    - Daily Diary, 2/1/79-2/25/80.
    - Calculations, 4/13/60-7/22/60.
    - Calculations, 11/26/59-3/13/60.
    - Library, 4/9/66-10/23/67.
    - Library, 1/20/69-5/26/70.
    - AISP, 6/17/67-10/21/67.
- E Series, Material to go with W. E. Lobo/M. W. Kellogg Files.
  Materials in this series were transferred to the Walter E. Lobo Papers, Ms85-014, in November 1987.
  - "The Improbable Achievement: Chemical Engineering at MIT."
  - "Large Scale Production of Oxygen - Combined Technical Oil Missions Holroyd Report - German Oil Technology."
  - "Guide to Refinery Operating Costs (Process Costimating)."
  - "The German Chemical Industry - A Bibliography of the Chemical, Metallurgical, and Process Industries."
  - "Enriched Air."
  - "List of Process Management's Translations of I. G. Reports - Set No. 46."
- F Series, Books, 1897-1925.
  - "Coal Tar and Ammonia" (Vols I - III) by George Lunge, 1916.
  - "Steampower Plant Engineering" by G. F. Gebhardt, 1925.
  - "The Elements of Steam Engineering" (Vol II). Prepared by The Colliery Engineer Company, 1897.